Oh I know what I'm supposed to do!
Fight for the
Fight for the way.
I can't wait to open the door,
I'll be able to open the door,
and I'll be able to open the door.
Let's start with the new world.
I've been waiting for a few years,
since I've been in the past,
But I'll never be able to
see you in front of you.
Don't forget, we'll fight together.
I don't have any
problem with that day.
I don't have any problems with that day.
I'll see you
next time.
We are pleased to report that our
victory salute and the execution accord
Sure are leaving us hanging, huh?
Is there a way to repair it?
Shh, sounds like it's clearing up.
The Whitebeard Pirates were defeated?
That means the good guys won, right?
Repeat, this is Navy Headquarters with an
update regarding the battle at Marineford.
Although Whitebeard and his allies made
the conflict a long and arduous affair,
the Marines struggled dilately
in the name of justice.
We are pleased to report that
our victory over Whitebeard was
absolute and the execution of
Hortgas D-Ace was carried out.
You are once again safe from
the treachery of pirates
thanks to the Navy and
world government's efforts.
We did it!
We're invincible!
No attempt at the power of the Navy!
Just you wait!
The people summoned me to
serve at HQ and I'll be ready.
Thank goodness the war's finally over.
Hooray!
I thought it never ends!
Whitebeard's reign of terror is over.
Party time!
The good guys beat the
bad ones, right, Mom?
That's right, and we
have the Navy to thank.
I knew they could do it!
Be sad, pirates!
I thought we were goners!
Now, three chairs, one
for the world government!
One for the emeralds, and a
big one for all the Marines!
Back at Marineford and far away from
celebrations of the Navy victory,
there are seven ships afloat.
Those who will soon take part
in the new pirate era are
witnessing one of the great
turning points in history.
Ever mindful of the Navy's
ruthless sense of justice,
they still stare upon
the aftermath of war.
Knowing the ensuing chaos will leave plenty
of opportunity for new powers to arise.
Captain Drake, sir.
At last, the war's over.
Both sides are weakened.
Navy and the pirates.
It's just a matter of time.
Whitebeard's territory.
Other pirates will be vying for control.
Oh, it's bound to get pretty rough.
Now, Blackbeard's reign has begun.
Not only has he built a formidable crew,
but he's got two Devil Fruit powers.
Just our luck,
it's gonna be a while before we've
got the strength to topple those guys.
It's all his fault.
Damn that Blackbeard.
I'll find him and make him pay.
All right, let's go! Yeah!
What the hell is going on?
What are you talking about, Captain?
Is something wrong?
Trafalgar Law is no friend of Straw Hat.
Why is he saving him now?
What's the catch?
Law has got a reputation.
He's one of the North
Blue's most brutal pirates.
There's no way he'd have saved him unless
he was expecting something back in return.
How odd.
Captain Hawkins, what
seems to be the matter?
I've been trying to determine if
Straw Hat Luffy is alive or dead,
but the cards won't say.
To tell you the truth, this war
had me pretty worked up at first.
Never thought the Great
Whitebeard would die.
Well, either way, it's over.
Yeah, guess so.
Nothing's ever over.
One old bastard kicks the bucket and
an even meaner one takes his place.
Blackbeard's gonna turn
everything upside down.
See before, the four
emperors ran the new world.
Whitebeard, Kaido, Big Mom, and Shanks.
But now that Whitebeard is dead,
everything is out of balance and no
one knows how the scales are gonna tip.
It's a brand-new hour, like none before.
And it's ours for the taking.
News of the Navy's victory
in the war at Marineford,
the deadliest battles since the
dawn of the Great Pirate Era,
spread like wildfire, and people across
the world are celebrating the good news.
The East Blue
Alright!
Whitebeard is dead at last!
Good riddance! You said it!
What a relief!
The West Blue
We can finally sail in peace!
Raise your glasses!
The South Blue Celebratory
sail over here! Over here too!
Get your body food!
I don't have a care in the world!
The North Blue
Oh, man, that really hit the spot.
Keep the drinks coming!
Next round is on the house!
The Grand Line.
Can we join the Navy, too?
I'm gonna beat all the pirates!
Uh-uh, I am!
Yeah, right!
Thank you.
And may this peace last.
As it goes with history, the
passage of time distorts facts?
and glosses over imported details.
Soon, the only two words that
stand out are Navy victory.
If lost in the celebration,
most people fail to consider
the war's real consequences.
What was that?
You're all fools!
Didn't you hear him?
The One Piece.
Whitebeard said it's real, so
Gold Roger wasn't lying after all.
Well, guess we better get to finding it!
Enough wasting away in this dump.
Time to set sail!
Though Navy victory might
have a nice ring to it,
it does not necessarily equate to peace.
You guys aren't welcome here!
Get out of our town!
For Whitebeard was a
pirate but he was also
a protector and news of
his death emboldened.
Pirates who previously
cowered from him don't worry
I've turned all the marines
on board into stone.
So what is Luffy's
condition will he be all
right can I help somehow anything at all?
Gosh I was afraid the
navy was still hot on
our tail but I don't
understand how did you know
the sub was going to
surface right here and now
I simply had Salome track
your ship underwater.
Oh don't change the
subject Luffy is all that
matters you're right
really dude oh captain
I did everything I
possibly could so does that
mean that he'll be okay
we'll just have to wait and
see he's in stable
condition for now however he
took on a lot more damage
than most could endure
and there's no guarantee
that he'll survive.
What an uplifting prognosis
who said that me duh
anyhow if you want straw
boy to wake up you're
gonna have to show him
some love we owe him our
lives so take good care
of him we'd still be in.
prison without his help.
Now all the new Kama can finally go to the
Kamabaka kingdom like
we've always dreamed.
Off we go!
Farewell, Straw Hat, we're heading home!
Yeah!
So, uh, who are they?
They are a group of
prisoners from Impel Down.
It appears that Luffy is their friend.
They must have snuck
onto the ship as well.
I can't believe he pushed his
body past its limit a second time.
That's how strong the bond was
between Straw Boy and Ace Boy.
You tell him, Eva.
Nothing can stop him then
and nothing can stop him now.
What?
I wish that were so,
but fate could be cruel.
You can't save everyone.
All of that work for nothing.
He's nearly dead because that's
the kind of world this is.
You get down now, Eva.
Straw Hat can pull through this.
I knew it.
You gotta live, Straw Hat.
Don't you dare die on us.
Luffy has touched so many lives.
If only there was some way I could
take his place so that he may survive.
Poor darling.
So lucky.
Must be nice having the pirate
empress fawn over you like that.
Yeah, wow.
You're a new face.
Are you one of Strawboy's pals?
No, I can't say why I saved him.
Or it's complicated at least.
Are you going to pressure
me for the details?
No, no.
Let's just say that your heart
guided you to his side. Hey, wait!
You can't walk around yet.
Don't push your body like that.
Captain told you to rest, remember?
Your wound could open up.
Come back here, please!
Leave me be.
Jinbei.
I know you.
Captain Law from the North Blue.
You look awful.
Should you really be
moving around like that?
I owe you.
I owe you my life.
Enough.
Lie down.
My mind is troubled.
Luffy, the pain I feel for
him is such that I can't rest.
I have failed you, friend.
Remorse.
If this is how I feel,
then just imagine him.
His collapse may have been a mercy
since it allowed us to take him away,
but what now?
Even if he survives, with
the immensity of his loss,
I fear for the moment he awakens.
You, the fuzzy one, where's
your transponder snail?
Who, me?
I'll go get it!
If you'd like.
No fair.
I wish I got to serve the Empress, too.
I will summon the Kuja ship so
we can sail across the Calm Belt,
even with this submarine.
The world government can't find out Luffy's
alive, or else they'll come after him.
Let us harbor him safely
at the Maiden Island.
Really?
As long as they still view me as a
warlord, Luffy will not be in danger there.
Fleet Admiral Sengoku!
I'm very sorry for the intrusion, sir.
But we've just received
urgent news from Impel Down.
Should I continue, sir?
Magellan, is he all right?
He was beaten badly and is barely alive.
The medical team has been
working on his injuries non-stop,
but Magellan is ashamed, and he's blaming
himself for what happened down there.
If his wounds weren't so severe, then he'd
probably be at risk of killing himself.
Don't tell me that nonsense.
He knows how much we need him.
Yes, sir. Of course.
What exactly did happen that impaled down?
Things there are quite disastrous.
The situation on level
six is especially dire.
It's a crisis.
Elaborate.
What's wrong, boys?
Feeling a bit down?
Thinking you'll be stuck
in this hellhole forever?
Just wait until you die, huh?
So how about this?
Start fighting!
Start fighting right
there in your jail cell!
Those of you who survive,
get a free ticket to join my crew
and sail out of here with me.
Is he for real?
It's time to play.
Now, who should I kill first?
See ya?
He had his pick of the deadliest
criminals in the world,
and he had them fight to the death!
while he simply stood there and watched?
Yes, but only four of
the prisoners were taken.
San Juan Wolf, Avalo Pizarro, Vasco
Schott, and Katarina Devon, as you saw.
But I'm sorry to say, sir,
that his new recruits aren't the only
prisoners who are missing from Level 6.
I...
So Impel Down is swimming with escaped
criminals, the worst the world has ever seen.
We can't let a single
one of them get away.
If they stole a ship and slipped
into some country unnoticed,
there's no telling what sort of
terrible things might happen.
Start a count of how many
level 6 prisoners are missing?
You have their names and put out a
most wanted list as soon as possible.
What's wrong?
Well, uh, actually.
I'm under direct orders
from the world government
to keep this matter a secret at any cost!.
A huge blunder like this one could
badly hurt the government's reputation?.
I don't give a damn!
Doflamingo, you bastard!
Come on, lighten up.
We both know you're too
weak to be a warlord.
Just face it.
I'll do you a favor for old time's sake.
We won't say the government
had you put down.
We'll say you gave your life in battle.
So Sengoku put you up to this.
I'll tear him apart. Nah.
Think higher up the ladder.
A pirate ship is approaching
Laskop in the West Blue,
but we don't have any
forces nearby that can help.
Contact the closest base.
Reinforcements from the 80th
Division are on their way.
This is the South Blue.
Currently checking the
location of the attack.
Damn it!
The pirates are supposed
to be afraid of us.
Headquarters dealt them a
major blow at Marineford.
Not to mention Whitebeard
is dead, so what gives?
You would have thought they'd
be laying low after the war,
but they're running wild everywhere.
I wonder what's gotten into those guys.
Pirates have started raiding Lost Cop.
Communication has also been lost.
Proceed to send backup.
I repeat, send backup now.
All right, boys, load her up.
After that, it's on to the Grand Line!
Yeah!
Two weeks after the War
of the Best concluded,
the world began to witness the
consequences of Whitebeard's defeat.
No!
You guys aren't welcome here!
Get out of our town!
You didn't hear the news?
Then let me tell you, this dump's been
up for grabs since Whitebeard croaked.
This stupid flag don't mean a thing now.
That's right.
There's no one to protect you now!
Hey, Twerp, listen up, because
I'm only going to say this once.
This island's under my control now.
The name's Brownbeard,
and don't you forget it.
The war ended with the death of
Whitebeard and a Navy victory.
Yet the peace that the world
government hoped to achieve slipped
through their fingers and the world
was only plunged into further unrest
Meanwhile, aboard the Kuja ship,
Boa Hancock, Gene Bay,
and the Heart Pirates make
their way toward Amazon
Lily Where they will shelter
the unconscious Luffy
Now then,
this chapter of Straw Boys Live co-starring
yours truly has come to a close Hee-haw!
Jinbei, I hope you don't mind
watching over our friend in my place.
Of course, my body is
still too weak to swim,
but the least that I can do is
watch over Luffy until he recovers.
Though, I fear there is precious
little aid I can give him.
It was a curious twist of fate
to meet you, Fishman. Likewise.
Although we were both imprisoned
in the lowest levels of Impel Down,
our paths nearly didn't cross.
Luffy carried us away like a tidal wave,
though I must admit I know not the
direction that these seas flow.
Tidal wave is right.
His antics at Marineford were
too turbulent even for us.
I hate to say goodbye, my friend,
but the candy boys and girls of my kingdom
can only wait on their master for so long.
Do take care of Strawboy for me!
I shall miss him!
So long, bye!
Thanks for everything, Straw Hat!
We'll tell tales of you in
Kamabaka Kingdom for years to come!
When he wakes up, be
sure to say hi for us!
Get real soon, Straw Boy!
We can't wait to see you again!
Right in there!
Everything's gonna be okay!
Let's go, my darlings! Yeah!
Off to the newcomer paradise!
Keep leading the way, Queen Eva! Yes, sir!
Peachy Island, here we come!
I hate to ruin the moment, but we
really should be on our way now.
Two weeks have passed.
Law and his crew are staying in the bay,
continuing to treat Luffy's injuries
without encroaching on the island.
Someone grab him he's
lost his mind what will
happen to him if he remains in that state?
Simple if he keeps
flailing around the more
likely he is to open his
wound and if that happens!
Chances are he'll die.
That was our chance!
Dammit, get off me!
Just hold still! Shut up! Let me go!
Where did they take you?
Where did you go?
He's gone completely mad.
Oh, Luffy.
We've got to tell the snake princess.
Princess!
We have big news! Are you there?
Luffy is finally woken up.
Luffy is awake! Are you sure?
Oh, thank goodness.
I must rush to his side
immediately. You cannot!
The kingdom is obsessed
with seeing those men.
How can you expect them to follow our laws
if you so readily break them yourself?
Men are prohibited in our land.
Luffy is one thing, but I cringe at how
easily we let these strangers into the bay.
Must you keep bending the rules?
Yes, I know, but he needs help.
Before worrying about that,
you should eat something.
Your sister's right.
Since you returned to Amazon Lily,
you've barely eaten a bite. Food?
Yes, Luffy must be starving
after his recovery.
He will need his strength.
Go prepare a mountain of
dishes rich in nutrients.
Yes, as you wish.
And I shall aid you myself.
Onward to the kitchen for Luffy.
Whatever you want, princess.
I can let this one pass.
So she wants to do some cooking.
You harm in that.
When we're done, I'll serve him myself.
Are you even listening?
When he gets well, we'll invite
Luffy to these chambers alone.
Show some self-restraint.
What nonsense.
I am an empress.
You can't tell me what to do.
No means no.
The well-being of this country
does not revolve around you.
You poor girl.
You've been stricken by the
most vile illness imaginable.
To think that our fearsome pirate
empress is lovesick of all things?
Luffy must have gone
through hell and back!
Surviving both Impel Down!
And the terrible things that
happened at Navy headquarters!
Despite my protest!
The fact that he made it back here
alive is nothing short of a miracle.
I can't help but wonder
what the gods expect of him?
Yo, pass me the wrench!
Okay, here you go.
Hey, how are the ship
repairs coming along?
We'll manage, don't you worry.
The rest of you ever figure
out where Straw Hat went?
Team Bay's been gone for a while now, too.
Nope, ain't got a clue.
Someone told me that if
a man enters Amazon Lily,
he'll be turned to
stone right on the spot.
I'm starting to think it's
worth dying for, though.
According to Afalandra,
there are tons of girls, way more
than what we saw at the port.
This is a one-time chance.
If I don't peek, I might regret
it for the rest of my life.
I guess we'll both be statues then, huh?
Do you think they've got girl bears?
You're ruining our fantasy!
Sorry I asked.
Amazon women are humans!
No bears for you!
Life is cruel.
What is this place?
Where am I?
Maybe I dreamt the whole thing.
Sorry, Luffy.
I tried.
But looks like this is as far as I can go.
It's not true!
It can't be!
Loopy!
Go away!
Stop it!
It's not true!
Oh, my God.
Jinbei, I know I might not
make it out of this alive.
I'm sorry, but if I die, would
you look after my brother for me?
You must listen to me, Luffy.
Your brother Ace is... Don't say it!
Don't say anything!
You think I don't know?
You think I think this is a dream?
If it were a dream, I'd already be awake.
But it's not, is it?
My brother Ace is really dead, isn't he?
Yes, I'm afraid that he is.
Hey, Grandpa, who's this Ace Fall?
Well, funny you should ask.
Because Ace is going to
be your new big brother.
Luffy, when next we meet,
we'll both be top pirates.
The top, you and me.
Ace!